direction 1  the boards as they ship                   exit 0  PASS, clean baseline
             boardsRead=3, visibleChars=6171, navItems=45, badges=45, tiles=12, lanes=18, sources=18, onMapRows=7, emptyPanels=5, meetingRows=4, annotations=5
             0 finding(s) on the shipped boards

direction 2  the same boards copied with nothing changed
             exit 0  PASS
             boardsRead=3, visibleChars=6171, navItems=45, badges=45, tiles=12, lanes=18, sources=18, onMapRows=7, emptyPanels=5, meetingRows=4, annotations=5
             57/57 self-tests inside check.mjs

PLANTED      a nav row names a lens the product does not export
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: not a lens "Zoning"
PLANTED      the roster loses a lens the product exports
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: missing "Parks"
PLANTED      a badge outside the ruling's five-word vocabulary
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: not one of the five the ruling names
PLANTED      NOT BUILT lands on a surface whose page does exist
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: and the surfaces whose page does not exist are
PLANTED      a work item the shell does not have
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: not a work item "Asset register"
PLANTED      a nav row states no disposition at all
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: carries no badge
PLANTED      a tile renders a zero
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: renders 0
PLANTED      a tile names nowhere to go
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: names nowhere to go
PLANTED      a tile shows a number and points at an absence
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: points at an absence
PLANTED      a tile shows a number with no arrow to it
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: renders no arrow
PLANTED      the region renders three tiles instead of four
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: renders 3 tile(s)
PLANTED      the lane roll-up counts a lane that is not reading
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: states "6 of 6 reading"
PLANTED      a lane claims a zero the city has not made
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: renders assets as 0
PLANTED      a quiet lane loses its basis line
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: renders no basis line
PLANTED      a quiet lane basis stops saying what is missing
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: does not say what is missing
PLANTED      a lane draws a number under a basis that says nothing was read
             on Sparse.dc.html  exit 1  caught: claiming a number nothing has read
PLANTED      a lane the ruling names is not rendered
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: not a lane "Utilities"
PLANTED      Connections is promoted on a pack that is granted a source
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: still promotes Connections above the decision queue
PLANTED      Connections is promoted on the granted pack
             on Sparse.dc.html  exit 1  caught: is granted 1 of 10 sources and still promotes Connections
PLANTED      Connections is demoted on a pack that is granted nothing
             on Empty.dc.html  exit 1  caught: is granted nothing and yet demotes Connections
PLANTED      a board stops stating how many sources are granted
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: states no granted-source count
PLANTED      the Sources panel comes back
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: renders a "Sources" panel
PLANTED      the map region is dropped from the rail
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: has no map region
PLANTED      the address lookup is dropped from the rail
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: has no address lookup
PLANTED      engine vocabulary leaks back onto a city-manager surface
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: prints the atom type "setback-rule"
PLANTED      an empty state loses the basis line under it
             on Empty.dc.html  exit 1  caught: renders no basis line
PLANTED      an empty state loses its headline
             on Empty.dc.html  exit 1  caught: renders no headline
PLANTED      a meeting row loses the Agenda link it is supposed to carry
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: Agenda link(s), and every meeting row carries one
PLANTED      the meetings panel stops naming the calendar it read
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: without naming the calendar
PLANTED      the not-read form is replaced by nothing on a quiet pack
             on Empty.dc.html  exit 1  caught: renders neither meeting rows nor the not-read form
PLANTED      the nav footer and the Connections chip disagree on grants
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: the Connections chip says 7 of 10
PLANTED      the located count falls under its own list
             on Main.dc.html  exit 1  caught: count is under its own list
PLANTED      an artboard appears on disk that this instrument does not declare
             on Print.dc.html  exit 1  caught: an artboard on disk that this instrument does not declare
PLANTED      a declared artboard is missing from disk
             on Sparse.dc.html  exit 1  caught: declared as an artboard and does not exist
PLANTED      the design record stops saying the map is pinned rather than designed here
             on README.md  exit 1  caught: is pinned rather than designed here
PLANTED      the canvas carries no annotation at all
             on canvas.json  exit 1  caught: carries no annotation
ABORT        ABORT the facts file is taken away and no verdict is issued
             on source-facts.json  exit 2  caught: source-facts.json is missing or unparsable
ABORT        ABORT the facts file loses the product label sets and the run refuses
             on source-facts.json  exit 2  caught: does not carry the product's nine lens labels
ABORT        ABORT the facts file loses the figure Connections is keyed on
             on source-facts.json  exit 2  caught: does not carry the figure the shipped placement function keys the Connections move on
ABORT        ABORT the facts file loses the three NOT BUILT rows read off the nav markup
             on source-facts.json  exit 2  caught: three roster rows the product's nav markup badges
ABORT        ABORT the honest-empty predicate matches nothing at all and the run refuses rather than passing
             on Sparse.dc.html + Empty.dc.html  exit 2  caught: REFUSING A VERDICT

evidence: instrument-report.json carries 11 matched-input counters, 5 note(s) and 0 finding(s)

41/41 planted violations caught, and the shipped boards pass the
check until one of them is planted.

EXIT=0
