baseline: check.mjs exits 0 on the unmodified fleet artboards

CAUGHT a status band the product does not declare (in a roster chip)
CAUGHT an invented state word in a nav badge
CAUGHT an operator reference the composer never produced (format-valid)
CAUGHT two roster rows swapped out of composer order
CAUGHT an uncatalogued fleet vendor named in prose
CAUGHT a money token on a generated-record surface

6 of 6 planted defects caught
artboard hashes after restoration: identical to before, all 2
  Main.dc.html  b361ecb44d725405e0210ead0f43042a
  Connected.dc.html  ba22084614191e52f66febac292b8043
final baseline re-run: exit 0
